ROOFTOP FIREWORKS AND FLEET OF RIVERBOATS CELEBRATE THE FIRST ELECTRONIC 'POUR' OF HEINZ'S GIANT NEON KETCHUP BOTTLE	16 Nov 1995	PITTSBURGH POST-GAZETTE
GIANT 'UNION OYSTER HOUSE' ROOF SIGN ERECTED TO BEACON MOTORISTS ON THE NEW CENTRAL ARTERY SKYWAY	18 Sep 1957	MASS. HIGHWAY ARCHIVAL RECORD
URTH CAFFE EXPANDS DOWNTOWN: ICONIC NEON SIGN WELCOMES FOODIES TO ARTS DISTRICT	18 Jul 2011	LOS ANGELES DOWNTOWN NEWS
MCSORLEY'S IS FORCED TO LET WOMEN IN; U.S. JUDGE RULES 114-YEAR-OLD TAVERN'S MALE-ONLY POLICY UNCONSTITUTIONAL	26 Jun 1970	THE NEW YORK TIMES
CHARIOTS OF HEALTH: ROME'S MIDNIGHT DRUGSTORES LIGHT UP THE DARK WITH NEW LUMINOUS GAS CROSSES	14 Nov 1928	IL MESSAGGERO
BILLIONAIRE'S FORTRESS: FIERCE GUARD DOGS AND WARNING SIGNS SECURE GETTY'S MALIBU HIDEAWAY	14 Oct 1957	LOS ANGELES TIMES
GIANT NEON SAW SIGN SPARKS MID-CENTURY BOOM AS HARDWARE OUTPOST MODERNIZES LINCOLN BOULEVARD	9 Jan 1949	THE EVENING OUTLOOK
A BOLD NEW OCULIS ON THIRD STREET: MARIO BOTTA’S TOWERING BRICK ICON READY TO REDEFINE THE SOMA SKYLINE	12 Jan 1995	THE SAN FRANCISCO EXAMINER
STATE OFFICIALS CITE FLASHING NEON RABBIT AS PUBLIC NUISANCE; DEMAND REMOVAL NEAR SIDEWALKS	28 Sep 1959	COLORADO HIGHWAY DEPT. BUREAU
BLAZING NEON OASES: MOTOR COURTS ALONG TUCSON’S 'MIRACLE MILE OF SAFETY' LIGHT UP THE DESERT HIGHWAY	5 Mar 1948	ARIZONA HIGHWAYS
EAST RIVER SPANS ABLAZE: THOUSANDS CHEER AS MAYOR TURNS MASTER SWITCH TO ILLUMINATE CITY'S NEWEST BRIDGE	31 Dec 1909	THE NEW YORK TIMES
THE 60-FOOT RED BEACON: UNION SQUARE SHOPPERS GUIDED BY DOWNTOWN’S LARGEST VERTICAL FABRIC SIGN	4 Dec 1971	SF HERITAGE RECORD
TRANSIT AUTHORITY TARGET: END CONFUSION OF SUBWAY SIGNS	31 Oct 1953	THE NEW YORK TIMES
GIANT NEON ARROW ANCHORS KAPAHULU AVENUE AS LEONARD'S BAKERY FLASHES OPEN MODERN NEW STOREFRONT	12 Sep 1957	KAPAHULU BUSINESS REVIEW
A RED NOSE FOR RUDOLPH: PORTLAND’S LEAPING SKYLINE STAG GETS A BRIGHT HOLIDAY SURPRISE	13 Nov 1959	THE OREGON JOURNAL
MALIBU PIER FLASHES BRILLIANT NEW NEON ARCHWAY TO WELCOME ANGLERS TO THE PACIFIC COAST HIGHWAY	14 Sep 1949	LOS ANGELES TIMES
MAYOR FRANK HAGUE PULLS MASTER SWITCH TO SET GIANT NEW WATERFRONT TIMEPIECE IN MOTION	1 Dec 1924	THE JERSEY JOURNAL
BALTIMORE SKYLINE CHANGES FOREVER AS NEW LED ENERGY-EFFICIENT DOMINO SUGAR SIGN IS TURNED ON	4 Jul 2021	THE BALTIMORE SUN
WALLAUER PAINT & DESIGN CELEBRATES CENTENARY OF SERVICE ACROSS WESTCHESTER COUNTY	14 May 2021	THE JOURNAL NEWS
GRAND CENTRAL SLATE TO BE ERASED FOR ELECTRONIC BOARD IN SPRING	15 Jan 1967	THE NEW YORK TIMES
GIANT ELECTRIC SHAMROCK BILLBOARD TOPS BEACON STREET TO ILLUMINATE KENMORE SQUARE	29 Jul 1940	THE BOSTON GLOBE
THE LEGEND OF THE BOND CLOTHING SIGN: REMEMBERING THE TIMES SQUARE NEON MASTERPIECE WITH REAL WATERFALLS	15 Feb 1948	THE NEW YORK TIMES
THE GRAN VIA IGNITES: GIANT NEON SCHWEPPES SIGN TURNS ON ATOP THE CARRION BUILDING FOR THE FIRST TIME	21 May 1972	ABC MADRID
THE TERRAZZA MARTINI SIGN: A SYMBOL OF GLAMOUR AND MILANESE APERITIVO CULTURE FOR GENERATIONS	11 Oct 1958	CORRIERE DELLA SERA
HOW THE OXO TOWER CLEVERLY BYPASSED LONDON'S STRICT 1930S ADVERTISING BAN USING ITS OWN WINDOWS	3 Aug 1930	THE DAILY TELEGRAPH
EROTIC GHERKIN' SAGS RUMOR DENIED AS TOWER'S CURVING STEEL FRAME RISES IN THE CITY	14 Oct 2002	THE GUARDIAN
"THE LONDON EYE GRANTED PERMANENT PLANNING PERMISSION, SOLIDIFYING ITS PLACE IN THE CAPITAL'S SKYLINE"	3 Jul 2002	THE TIMES
STAR FERRY PIER RELOCATION SPARKS PROTESTS AND NOSTALGIA OVER HONG KONG'S DISAPPEARING HERITAGE	11 Nov 2006	SOUTH CHINA MORNING POST
"NEW HI-HO MOTEL OPENS NEAR MERRITT PARKWAY, LIGHTING UP BLACK ROCK TURNPIKE"	24 May 1960	THE BRIDGEPORT POST
HELMS NAMED OFFICIAL BAKER OF 1932 OLYMPIC GAMES; FAMOUS NEON SIGN TO BEAR OLYMPIC RINGS	15 Jun 1932	LOS ANGELES TIMES
NEW PADRE HOTEL WILL CREATE A NEW SKYLINE FOR BAKERSFIELD	10 Aug 1927	THE BAKERSFIELD CALIFORNIAN
BEST WESTERN OUTLINES ROYAL TREATMENT FOR ROAD TRAVELERS: CROWN LOGO ADOPTED TO IDENTIFY MEMBER PROPERTIES	15 May 1962	THE ARIZONA REPUBLIC
THE DEATH OF THE MIDNIGHT SIGN-OFF: HOW THE TELEVISION TEST PATTERN BECAME AN ICONIC POP CULTURE RELIC	1 Sep 1997	BROADCASTING & CABLE
